Do not hide from the Lord
nor refuse his command.
Preserve my soul, for I am holy.
Save your servant
who trusts in you, my Lord.
Saint Michael the Archangel,
defend us in battle.
Be our protection against the wickedness
and snares of the devil.
I earnestly pray that,
as God has commanded, you drive him away.
I exorcise you
in the name of Jesus Christ.
Reveal yourself!
Who are you?
Tell me your name!
Stop it, you crazy bastard!
Dad!
Dad, save me!
- I seek power from the Lord
- Dad! Save me!
who conquered Satan,
grant us power...
So-mi!
- Dad!
- I'm right here!
- Can you hear me?
No, honey!
Stop it!
How many have you killed?
- So-mi! It's Dad!
- Dad!
I can't take it anymore!
So-mi!
Joon, are you okay?
Dad!
Dad, save me!
Save me!
It's...
over now.
So-mi, sweetie?
So-mi?
It's me, Dad. I'm here.
- Dad.
- Yeah, it's me.
Am I okay now?
Yeah, you're okay. You're okay now.
- I'm sorry.
- So-mi.
I'm so sorry.
So-mi, are you okay?
I'm sorry.
- It's over now.
- It's all my fault.
- I'm sorry. Breathe.
- I'm so proud of you.
Are you okay?
- What's going on? What's happening?
- So-mi!
It's Dad. I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, sweetie!
So-mi...
- So-mi.
- So-mi!
What's going on?!
- What's happening?
- So-mi, wake up!
- So-mi!
- Honey, do something!
Wake up!
Oh no.
So-mi!
So-mi, please breathe!
- So-mi!
- Sweetie!
So-mi!
No!
So-mi, breathe!
Breathe!
Alkaid.
Mizar.
Then Alioth.
Alioth.
Next, Megrez.
Then...
- Phecda?
- Phecda.
Merak.
Times two.
Times two!
One, two, three, four,
five, six!
That one. That's mine, Polaris.
It's mine.
I called dibs on it first.
Come on, it's mine.
Fine, it's yours.
All right, then. I'll be generous.
Let's share it.
Sounds good.
We can share it.
By the way, Dad,
Polaris will die someday too, right?
I'm asking this out of curiosity,
but how long can I live?
What do you mean?
You're my doctor,
so you should be honest with your patient.
You'll live longer than Polaris,
for tens of thousands of years.
Longer than Polaris?
Of course.
Cha So-mi.
She's your daughter, right, Dr. Cha?
The immediate cause of death
was cardiac arrest.
I see she had dilated cardiomyopathy,
and it's been about four months
since the heart transplant surgery.
DEATH CERTIFICATE
I hereby pronounce
Cha So-mi dead
at 5:19
on December 7, 2023.
Confirmed.
FIRST DAY OF BURIAL: THE DEATH
No, Mom.
It's too last minute to fly in.
The surgery went well...
I don't know.
I really don't know!
So-mi...
Excuse me, sir?
I wanted to ask you just in case...
So-mi!
When someone passes away
at such a young age like your child,
sometimes a simple ceremony is held
instead of a three-day funeral.
I mean,
some people prefer
a one-day funeral instead.
What nonsense is this?
My baby.
You expect me to send
my precious granddaughter off
with a simple ceremony?
Even a 300-day funeral wouldn't be enough.
We raised that child with so much love...
I should be dead instead.
Seung-do.
She had so many years ahead of her.
What in the world happened?
You said the surgery went well.
Seung-do.
So-mi...
My baby...
Hello?
Sir?
One second.
It's got to be fixed immediately.
Will it be possible?
What the...
Cat got your tongue?
Don't signal me with your finger.
Could you be quiet?
Still not working?
Yeah, it's not fixed yet.
Pardon me,
the mortuary chamber is broken,
but we're in the middle of fixing it,
so please don't worry.
My goodness.
I've never seen
anything like this in my life.
It's strange.
We must loosen the stiffness
in the body to proceed.
And considering the time of death,
rigor mortis should've already set in.
It's just her right hand.
It's the only part of her body
that's still stiff.
What's that?
Polaris.
How is that Polaris?
Look closely, this is Polaris.
It's so pretty.
Don't...
put her inside the chamber.
Sorry?
So-mi doesn't like being cold.
Right.
Well, the thing is...
SEOUL CENTRAL HOSPITAL
My deepest condolences.
Where's Dr. Cha?
He should be here somewhere.
Let me give him a call.
There's no need.
We're leaving soon anyway.
FUNERAL HOME
I heard Dr. Cha's daughter was already
in cardiac arrest when she got here.
I thought the surgery went perfectly.
What happened?
Perfect, my ass.
Then why did she die?
So much for always
boasting about his skills, huh?
It'll be a long surgery.
Take a deep sleep,
and wake up when I say, "So-mi, wake up."
Okay.
Think of me as Polaris
and never lose your way.
Okay.
What if, for some reason,
I don't wake up?
That'll never happen.
Don't you trust me?
I've never made a single mistake
in my entire life.
I only trust the heart.
In that case, I'll only trust you.
Nurse Jung said she changed
after the surgery.
She had delirium or something.
That's nonsense.
She was...
possessed.
We're doctors,
so we can't say that out loud.
She needed a shaman, not a doctor.
That's so scary.
Let's begin.
Thrust Satan and vile souls
that roam the world
back to hell!
Sister...
Please save me.
Am I okay now?
I exorcise you
in the name of Jesus Christ.
Reveal yourself.
Tell me your name!
Bariel!
My yediny...
Tell me your name!
Bariel!
My yediny...
Hae-sin.
By the way, ma'am.
So-mi
probably went to heaven, right?
You're hilarious.
You bullied her like crazy,
saying she was possessed.
Kim Mi-young.
What?
Am I wrong?
You all saw her.
He ended up like that
because So-mi pushed him.
Don't you remember?
- You all got dementia?
- Hey!
Quiet down.
How's your arm?
It's fine.
I'm getting my cast removed soon.
So-mi was so sorry about it.
She said you got hurt because of her.
I don't think
it was her who did this.
That day...
So-mi
was acting strange.
What do you mean?
I know.
That day, she wasn't So-mi.
Die!
You also know
how So-mi changed after the surgery.
What's wrong?
So-mi.
Let go! Die!
- So-mi!
- Let go!
So-mi!
Let go!
- What's with you?
- Let go!
How many have you killed?
So-mi, please.
You're a doctor who won't save people
unless they pay up!
- So-mi, please.
- Money is all you care about!
- Let go!
- So-mi!
- Die!
So-mi, it's okay.
It's okay.
Dad, it wasn't me.
It wasn't me.
What's wrong?
- Hey!
Are you okay? Hey.
Help!
Oh, no!
Someone help!
Over here!
Breathe.
Cough it out!
Breathe!
Are you okay?
Can you breathe?
Is that hair?
CHA SO-MI
LUCIA CHA SO-MI
It's me, Dad.
So-mi.
It's me.
Dad.
I'm cold.
Who did this to you?
I told you not to put her in.
But if the body rots...
You can't do this.
I told you not to put her in.
I'll take full responsibility,
so don't put her in.
Wait, you can't do this.
I'll take responsibility.
Hey, come on now. Easy.
Goodness me.
I understand.
I'll give you some time,
so please say goodbye one last time.
Could I at least get my flashlight back?
SECOND DAY OF BURIAL: THE CONGREGATION
This is not a matter to be taken lightly.
Even the diocese says
they won't overlook it this time.
I told you, didn't I?
He caused Michael to end up like that too.
Father Bahn needs to resolve his own suffering first.
Once-possessed priests suffer
each time they perform an exorcism.
What nerve does he have
to become an exorcist priest?
If you're curious, ask him yourself.
Ask him that exact question
you just asked me.
Defend our lamb from Satan.
Offer our prayers
in the sight of the Most High...
Don't!
Don't worry about it.
It is up to you to decide
whether you become a beast or a human.
I don't worry.
You know that the only thing
I care about is the demon.
I decided to hold a requiem mass
at the child's funeral.
I found out the demon's name
and banished it with the exorcism prayer.
Hae-sin.
That child has already gone
to the Lord's embrace.
I understand how you feel,
but it's time to let her go.
By any chance,
do you know the phrase "my yediny"?
It means "We are one" in Russian.
I'm certain the exorcism was a success,
but there was something else.
What is it?
Hae-sin.
You need to step back from this case.
I'll formally request assistance
from the Vatican.
No, I'll do it myself.
It's not a demon you can handle!
It wasn't just Bariel inside, was it?
Tell me, what exactly is it?
How can it stay
in the body of the deceased?
Just drop it!
- Father!
- Do I have to lose you too?
Our mission isn't to chase demons.
It's to save those
who are deceived by demons.
But you aren't even looking
at them right now!
Not looking? Me?
But I did.
I saw how Michael died
and how much So-mi suffered.
That's why I can't stop.
I will banish the demon,
no matter what it takes.
SEOUL CENTRAL HOSPITAL
So-mi...
So-mi!
The family members can come in now.
Oh gosh, So-mi.
Oh no!
Oh, no.
She looks so pretty.
Even if the deceased has already
closed their eyes and mouth,
their ears are said to be
the last to close.
If there are any last words
you wish to say,
please don't hold back and say them now.
So-mi.
I woke up in a rush this morning.
I looked at the clock,
worried that you'd be late for school,
but I realized I wasn't at home.
So-mi...
Dad.
My sweet child...
- Move. Move out of the way!
- What's wrong?
So-mi.
- Honey.
- So-mi, I'm here.
Open your eyes.
- What's with you?
- Open your eyes, So-mi.
- She talked. I heard her!
- Seung-do, that's enough!
Don't touch me!
- So-mi. So-mi, sweetie?
- Honey.
Look, she's crying.
She's crying.
Don't you see?
Stop it, Seung-do.
- So-mi, I'm here.
- Sir.
In rare instances, tears can flow
from the eyes of the deceased.
- So-mi.
- Please calm down.
I'm here, sweetie.
Calm down.
A virgin of Nazareth
conceived conjoined twins.
The first was named Bariel,
and the second was born without a name.
The demon that resurrected
through the bodies of the twins,
bewitched the hearts of the people
and led them to kill and be killed.
Unable to witness
their evil deeds any longer,
the priests sealed the younger
within the elder, Bariel's heart,
which prevented the evil
from ever regaining its power again.
Bariel's heart...
The encoffining must be running late.
Let's begin quickly.
But the Sister hasn't arrived yet.
We must proceed now
to subdue its power even a little.
- Why are you doing this to me?
- Honey.
- Let go. Let go of me!
- Seung-do.
Grace and peace to you from God our Father
and the Lord Jesus Christ,
and also with your spirit.
- And also with the priests.
- Let go!
- Dad!
- For your...
- ...eternal rest
- Grant unto her
- Eternal...
So-mi, breathe!
So-mi!
Open your eyes!
- Comfort...
- What's wrong, Father?
- Father!
- What are you doing, Father?
So-mi!
- Father!
- So-mi.
So-mi, it's me.
So-mi.
So-mi!
Can you hear me? So-mi!
What's the matter with him?
So-mi, open your eyes!
Hurry!
Can you hear me?
Open your eyes!
Dammit, Dr. Cha!
What's wrong, Father? Please stop!
Father!
So-mi!
- Let me go! So-mi!
- Please calm down!
Let go!
- No! So-mi!
- Please stop!
- Father, are you okay?
- Father!
Please wake up!
Father!
What's going on?
He...
Hae-sin...
Yes, Father.
When you focus on chasing demons,
you see nothing but demons.
Go show them.
Show them that demons can't defeat us.
Father.
You wretched, worthless servant!
No matter how hard you try,
you'll never defeat us!
Hurry!
Talk to me.
- What's happening here?
- What's the matter with you?
Sir, I'm begging you!
- Please, let me do this!
- Stop!
- Stop already!
- What's going on?
- Let me go!
- Honey, have you gone mad?
- I have to go!
- Where?
- I have to go to So-mi!
- What are you talking about?
She's talking to me!
- Honey!
- I have to go!
Stop it.
Look at me!
Honey.
So-mi's gone.
She's dead.
She's gone.
Just look at this. Is he trying to give me
a hard time or what?
What a nutjob.
He made a mess.
He's going to bitch at me
for putting her back in there.
Who are you?
You're not allowed to barge in here.
Looks like you're a priest.
Get out of here.
I'm going to call security.
Go ahead.
Call security.
Go call them.
This isn't a place where just anyone
can come and go as they please.
So why is everyone coming around?
Is he dead or something?
No, he isn't.
Why is he causing such a ruckus?
Who does he think he is?
What's your problem?
Why do you keep lurking around?
- What the hell is your problem?
- Goodness.
Don't do this. Let him go.
You can talk it out.
Honey, what's that...
What's wrong with So-mi?
What the...
The fact that the dead body
is reacting to holy water
means the demon is still inside So-mi.
Where did So-mi's transplanted heart come from?
We need to know that to find clues
about the demon inhabiting that heart.
Otherwise,...
it will be reborn through So-mi's body.
And the first targets
will be the family members.
What are you talking about?
Just as Jesus resurrected
on the third day,
the demon inside her will rise again
after three dawns from the day So-mi died.
Are you saying So-mi will come back to life?
No.
The demon will resurrect
using So-mi's body.
To get rid of the demon,
we must...
burn her body.
Dad.
I'm cold.
So-mi is dead.
Shut up.
Stay away from her,
or I'll kill you.
Get the hell out.
Get him out of here.
Honey.
Honey!
We found a heart.
Really?
We found a beautiful heart for you.
That's awesome!
Remove the heart from a living person?
You want me to give her the heart
of a burn victim of unknown origin?
You bastard!
Shut the hell up!
You'll perform the surgery,
so no one will know.
Why are you being so difficult
when it's about saving your child?
Go on.
Aren't you going to save your daughter?
Where did So-mi's transplanted heart come from?
We need to know that to find clues
about the demon inhabiting that heart.
Otherwise,
it will be reborn through So-mi's body.
Where did you get So-mi's heart?
Tell me, asshole!
What have you done? Tell me!
The entire hospital knows
that you've lost your mind.
Stop it now.
I don't know exactly either.
I just set it up.
I heard it came from a fire
in Dongducheon.
The donor was a Russian girl,
and she and her mother
were undocumented immigrants.
There's a Russian hideout
called Mother Teresa in Dongducheon.
Look for Big Mama there.
That's all I know.
MOTHER TERESA
Who are you?
Where's Big Mama?
- How does he know Big Mama?
- It's dangerous. Piss off.
Hail Mary, full of grace.
The Lord is with thee,
blessed art thou among women,
and blessed is the fruit
of thy womb, Jesus.
Pray for us sinners,
now and at the hour of our death.
Amen.
What took you so long?
You probably want to believe
you can still save her.
The more you try,
the more he comes to life.
To awaken and resurrect him
from his slumber,
we came here,
fleeing from the Russian Orthodox Church.
Worship and revere.
He wants blood.
On the third day after his death,
he will awaken and resurrect.
He will drench the whole world
in blood and darkness.
Bariel's heart...
started beating in my daughter's body.
Finally, we could serve the one
we longed for so much.
However...
the Russian Orthodox Church
kept interfering until the end.
So we needed a new vessel.
Tell me.
Who are you?
Who's this guy?
Why my daughter?
Tell me!
It's because of you.
He knew you'd do whatever it took
to save your daughter.
You thought you found the heart.
But no.
We found the vessel.
You satanic bastards!
Tell me.
Tell me how I can extract the demon
from her body and save her.
Tell me! Untie this!
It's over for you,
no matter how much you try.
You have to disappear
for your daughter to let go of everything
and live forever in his embrace.
Aren't you elated?
She'll come back to life.
Stop!
Begone, Satan!
The cross of the holy father Benedict.
May the holy cross be our light.
Do not let the demon rule over us.
Begone, Satan!
By the will of the Lord, tell me,
what is the name of your master?
I have to go to his side.
Your murderer!
Surrender to the Lord and speak.
What is his name?
lg...
mael...
What are you trying to do?
Get it together.
That demon is trying to use you
and resurrect himself.
Move.
We have to burn it.
That's not So-mi. It's the devil!
Hae-sin.
The Lord has spoken,
"The light shines in the darkness,
and the darkness has not overcome it."
Seok-joon.
Stop.
Stop it...
Just kill me.
Kill me.
Our Father in heaven,
defend our lamb from Satan.
We offer our prayers to the Most High,
that his endless mercy
may quickly reach us.
It's no use.
Seize the dragon
and the ancient serpent...
Don't!
Amen.
What's shaking your heart
is not the devil,
but your feelings for Michael.
Your heart is clouding your eyes and ears,
giving the devil an opportunity.
Lamb of God, who takes away
the sins of the world,
have mercy on us.
Lamb of God, who takes away
the sins of the world,
grant us peace.
Bahn Hae-sin!
Hae-sin.
I'm not going to give up on you.
So don't ever give up.
No...
No!
I shall not fear for there is light.
For you, my God, are with me,
I shall not fear.
What did you do
when you got lost as a kid?
Stay put.
That's right.
Stay put until I find you.
Understand? Promise?
I promise.
Please say your farewell.
Moment of silence.
DAY THREE OF OF BURIAL: THE PROCESSION
Just look at the time.
Excuse me, ma'am.
I'm sorry,...
but we can't delay any longer,
as it's almost time for the cremation.
We really need to leave now.
Mother.
We won't be able to
finish the funeral at this rate.
Shouldn't he be here
to see his child off?
Did you trip?
- No. I can't lift it.
- Try again.
- One, two, three!
Seung-do.
What are you doing?!
The coffin is moving!
I'm here.
- Dr. Cha!
- Sir!
Let's go.
All right, let's go.
Just hold on.
Move! Get out of the way!
- Sir!
- Seung-do.
- Move!
- What do we do?
What are you doing?
Are you out of your mind?!
- Please don't do this!
- Let go of me!
- Please calm down!
- Let go!
- You can't do this!
- Let me go!
Don't touch me!
Let go!
Someone stop him!
You can hear me, right, So-mi?
When did that priest get here?
- Honey!
- Enough already!
- Don't do it!
- Stop it!
Saint Michael the Archangel,
defend us in battle.
Be our protection against the wickedness
and snares of the devil.
I earnestly pray that,
as God has commanded, you drive him away.
Archangel Michael,
leader of the heavenly hosts,
cast away Satan and all evil spirits,
who roam around the world
seeking to destroy souls...
Dad!
So-mi!
Lord, the savior of those who seek you.
I ask you to...
vanquish every presence
and satanic machination.
So-mi!
So-mi, where did you go?
- What happened?
- So-mi!
- What's going on?
- Where did she go?
- So-mi!
- Where is she?
Where did she go?
Think of me as Polaris
and never lose your way.
Okay?
Okay.
So-mi.
Where are you, So-mi?
It's me, Dad.
I'm right here.
So-mi.
So-mi?
Remember the promise I made to you?
I told you I'd stay put...
and wait for you...
if I ever lost you.
But...
I don't think I can hang on anymore.
No, So-mi.
I'm sorry.
Dad!
So-mi.
So-mi!
Where are you? So-mi!
Where are you?
It's me, Dad!
Are you okay?
Oh jeez.
What do I do?
What am I supposed to do?
She said she wouldn't give up.
She said she was going to wait for me
and never give up.
Hae-sin.
I will never give up on you.
Please save me.
You're a priest.
You must know what to do.
If So-mi...
is still hanging on in there,
then we don't have much time.
We need to save her quickly.
I'll start the exorcism prayer,
but I can't do it alone.
I need someone to receive the prayer.
No matter what happens,
you must endure until the end.
HOLY BIBLE
Close your eyes.
Cleanse the sins with this holy water,
cast out demons,
and repel the temptations of evil.
Amen.
Don't be deceived
no matter what you hear and see.
You must repel them with strong faith.
The Lord said,...
"The light shines in the darkness,
and the darkness has not overcome it."
In the name of the Father, the Son,
and the Holy Spirit.
Jesus the savior.
My Lord, my God, my everything.
Through your blood, we pray.
Through your cross, we pray.
Behold the cross of the Lord.
Begone, powers of demons!
So-mi!
Begone!
Begone from my daughter!
- Lord, hear our prayer.
- Obey and submit!
Obey and submit to the power of God,
not the devil!
Don't be deceived.
Stay alert.
Let my prayer and our cries
reach the Lord!
From now on,
the devil will try even harder.
Don't give it any openings.
Hurry.
Come on.
The next verse.
So-mi...
Dad...
We beseech you, Lord.
Be with us so that...
So-mi!
...we may no longer fear evil.
Holy and almighty Lord!
Grant us strength!
Give us the strength to overcome evil!
Your daughter is already dead.
Bring back my daughter.
Bring her back!
- Die.
- So-mi!
Die!
- Die!
- No!
Protect us in our struggle
and shield us from the wickedness
and snares of the devil.
In the name of Satan!
Vile demons,
release this child and begone!
- Submit to the power of the devil.
- Dad!
Cast this sinful child
into the fires of hell!
Deliver us from all the traps
of the evil spirit.
Beelzebub, we no longer fear Jesus!
Stay with me.
It's not real.
God, and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ,
through the intercession
of the blessed apostles Peter and Paul
and all the saints,
deliver me from evil
and protect me from Satan
and all evil spirits...
Kill me!
Thank you.
...that roam to harm
and corrupt souls!
- Kill me!
- Dad!
Dad, don't!
Don't do it!
Dad, stop it!
We're almost done.
We now have to call its name
and fully cast it out.
You are defeated, so give up and leave.
I now call your name and command you.
Begone from this child of God!
You demon!
Igma...
So-mi.
Can you hear me?
What do I have to do?
What do I have to do, So-mi?
Can you hear me?
Do you want to save your child?
Then prove it.
You're just a human
who only cares about yourself.
You killed that poor girl
to save your daughter.
Stab your heart deeply...
so that you and I can become one.
Only then will your daughter live again.
Beg!
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
So-mi.
Can you hear me?
So-mi!
Excuse me!
This is the security team. There's someone
who collapsed in the boiler room.
So-mi...
- Go get help!
- Yes, sir.
So-mi, can you hear me?
She's still unconscious,
but her breathing, temperature,
and heart rate are all normal.
We've never seen a case like this before.
Let's keep her stable
and monitor her condition closely.
Thank you so much.
It looks like a compound fracture.
Prepare the CT scan, please.
The demon starts its rebirth
by killing the person
its host loved the most.
And the first targets
will be the family members.
Wait a minute.
I'll help you.
No!
Thank you for waiting.
I kept my promise, right?
I'm sorry.
So-mi.
ONE YEAR LATER
Honey.
CHA SEUNG-DO
You've waited a while, right?
I'm sorry we couldn't come more often.
Father!
I don't...
remember everything,
but I remember a little.
I was really scared,...
but I saw a faint light.
And then I heard my dad's voice.
So I stayed put and waited
because I promised him I'd do so.
Are you okay?
I felt like I shouldn't be okay.
I couldn't help but think...
that he died because of me.
I hated myself for living...
instead of him.
No.
That's why you should be even more okay.
Your father is probably watching you.
You have to live the life he gave you
even more earnestly.
So-mi!
See you next time, Father Michael.
Let's go.
Come on.
Dad.
So-mi.